
const data = [
    {
      "question": "question 1",
      "answer": "answer 1",
      "id": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "question 2",
      "answer": "answer 2",
      "id": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "question 3",
      "answer": "answer 3",
      "id": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "question 4",
      "answer": "answer 4",
      "id": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "question 5",
      "answer": "answer 5",
      "id": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "question 6",
      "answer": "answer 6",
      "id": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "question 7",
      "answer": "answer 7",
      "id": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "question 8",
      "answer": "answer 8",
      "id": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "question 9",
      "answer": "answer 9",
      "id": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "question 10",
      "answer": "answer 10",
      "id": "10"
    }    
  ]
  export default data;